Madhuri Sripathi
Banglore, Karnataka, Karnataka - Email me on Indeed:
indeed.com/r/MadhuriSripathi/04a52a262175111c

Around 4 years of IT experience in analysis, testing and scripting on L2/L3 layer protocols and designing testcases and automating the same in TCL/TK and Python.

- Expertise in Networking Protocols L2, L3 protocols, Manual, Performance, Platform, Regression and Automation Testing.
- · Experience in python scripting and PYATS framework.
- \bullet Coordinating with onsite/offsite teams in resolving the defects found in Testing and working on

queries raised by customers..

- Reviewing the automated scripts.
- ${}^{\bullet}$ Exposure to Networking Protocols such as DHCP, OSPF, RIP, VLAN, STP/RSTP, LACP, TCP/IP,

IPv4, Ipv6, Ethernet.

- Automation in Python.
- ullet Excellent ability to plan, organize and prioritize my work to meet on time the deadlines of my

clients and keep customer's satisfaction at the highest level possible.

 ${\boldsymbol \cdot}$ Proven ability in quick understanding and learning of new technologies and their application

in business solutions

 ${\mbox{\tiny \bullet}}$ Good debugging and problem solving skills with excellent understanding of system

development methodologies, techniques and tools.

- Highly motivated team member with strong communication, analytical and organizational skills.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Strong communication, interpersonal and analytical skills with proficiency at grasping new

concepts quickly and utilizing the same in a productive manner.

- Willingness and ability to quickly adapt to new environment.
- Good positive attitude and ability to learn new things independently.
- ${}^{\bullet}$ Worked as Senior project engineer in Wipro Technologies, from Jan2014 to till date.

Languages: C

Network Analysis Tools: QDDTS, GNS3, IXIA, SPIRENT, PAGENT

Routing protocols VLAN, ETHECHANNELSTP, RSTP, RIP, EIGRP, OSPF, BGP,

MPLS, L2VPN, L3VPN,

IPSEC and MULTICAST.

Scripting Language Perl, Tcl/TK, Python

Traffic Generators IXIA, PAGENT, SPIRENT

Management Protocols Telnet, SNMP

Willing to relocate to: UAE - Dubai - abu-dabhi

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior project engineer

Cisco - Bengaluru, Karnataka -

March 2014 to Present

https://www.indeed.com/r/Madhuri-Sripathi/04a52a262175111c?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=INhttps://www.indeed.com/r/Madhuri-Sripathi/04a52a262175111c?isid=rex-

download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

Cisco 7600 is a router which supports both layer2 and layer3 protocols. It mainly deploys protocols

like MPLS and having specific modules to support the protocols IPSEC. Worked as system testing,

performance testing, stress testing and regression testing for all the IOS release on all layer 2 and layer 3 protocols.

Wipro Technologies Limited (Bangalore, Karnataka) Senior project engineer (March 2014 till date)

Senior software engineer

Wipro -

February 2014 to Present

Responsibilities:

- \bullet Responsible for regression and Manual testing of CISCO IOS -7600
- Test case execution, test case results tracking, debugging, logging defects in CDETS,

reproductions and fix verification.

• Configuration and Testing on Routing protocols OSPF, BGP, OSPF, MPLS, L3VPN, L2VPN, IPSEC,

QOS, SNMP and MULTICAST features on Cisco 7600 Routers.

 ${f \cdot}$ Filed critical bugs of high severity, through root cause analysis and effective testing methods

Bug verification, Bug tracking, and documentation and review bug fixes.

 \bullet Engaged in regression testing, filing bugs against Cisco IOS images to improve the quality of

the images and send weekly test reports.

- \bullet Mentoring of new joiners in the team and conducting technical training sessions.
- Responsibility for the 7600 platform customer queries (AT&T, Bharati, Vodafone, German IT,
- ullet Involved in Sev1, Sev2 and sev3 cases and MW related to L2/L3 Features.
- Create a Local Repro of the issue which was raised by the customer.
- ${\boldsymbol \cdot}$ Analyzed the customer issues and will provide the solutions to the customers
- ullet Worked with Developer to verify the DDTs fix for the customer Found Defects
- System Testing on every New IOS build for the L2/L3 protocols.
- Configuration and Testing on routing protocols
- · Working on Functionality, Scalability and Performance testing
- Preparing of Test beds and topologies using Line cards SIP200, SIP400, SIP600, ES+, ES20, GIG

and TenGig Lancards, pagent, IXIA Traffic generators etc. to create customer setup in local Labs

• Knowledge on TCL scripting and automated customer found issues into regression testing and also able to troubleshoot the script issues.

EDUCATION

Master degree in computer science in computer science

PES college

S.S.C in computer science

Rajah college

SKILLS

LINUX (4 years), UNIX (4 years), ospf (4 years), bgp (4 years), mpls (4 years), ipsec (4 years), multicast (4 years), 12vpn (4 years), 13vpn (4 years), tcl (4 years), python (2 years)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Operating Systems: LINUX, UNIX

Other protocols ARP, RARP, ICMP, ospf, bgp, mpls, 12vpn, 13vpn

Automaton tools: tcl,python